If the customer wants to track the status of his claim
then use I Will Take Care app.  Then
after that Health Assistance Service, as you might have seen
written here in the presentation,
second opinion is required.  The
second doctor had told the customer that he would insert a stent.
Now he needs a second opinion.  He is
in a dilemma whether he is saying the right thing or not.
So he should upload all his documents on I Will Take
Care App and you know from the customer, we will
provide him a second opinion whether he should do it or not, if you want to get
deals and discounts on medicines then I Will Take
Care App, if you want to
book diagnostic tests then I Will Take
Care App, if you want to book ambulance then I Will Take
Care App, even if you want to see the network list then
I Will Take Care App and now you know now we have come up
with the initiative called Il
Sahayak ISI Icic Labard ka banda hai.
What is his objective?
Why did we start it?  You know the
objective behind this initiative
is that we can provide ground support to the customers
inside the hospital.  He should be provided hospital support.
Medical assistance should be provided
in the hospital.  Now
I asked all of you why should someone take a health policy
?  What are the expectations?  So
everyone said that I should get the claim.  Claims
received on time.  So the customer does
not face any problem at the time of claim.  We will
provide him hospital assistance there.  That
oil assistant will visit him.  If there is any problem or
issue in his claims,
he will be helped in settling it.
Documents are not being arranged.
Each oil assistant even got the documents
picked up.  So this is the initiative that we have
started.  Why am I telling you
all these things
inside Elevat?  Because when you give this application to our customers,
it is a very excellent and
beautiful application that we have for our
customers.  Tell them that you
can use many services from here.  Like
my customer can avail 30% discount at the time of renewal.  If they
follow wellness programs on the I Will Take Care app, use it.  So I will take
care of how much you are walking.
If you participate in cyclothon, marathon or any of the health activities,
you are given points.  Those
points are visible to you on the same Oil Tech Care app,
which you can
redeem at the time of renewal and avail discount up to 30% by using Mera Customer.
Now let us talk about
its hero features.  The features that
differentiate our products
from the rest of the competition.  So as you all were
saying, Infinite Care is everyone's favorite.
So my favorite is also Infinite Care.
When this Infinite Care came, I thought, is there
some magic?  Meaning a policy of Rs 10 lakh will
provide a cover of Rs 1 crore.  Yes, I will
give the claim.  So but it actually this is what is
happening in the alleyways.  So infinite
claim means no matter how big the claim is, we will
settle it for you.  But we will settle it for you only once
during the entire policy tenure.
So the
customer himself will decide when he wants to
take it.  Once taken, it will be
removed from your policy.  You won't be able to take it again.